# Arielle Dameshghi

## Bio

With 5 years of administrative experience in publishing, healthcare, and education settings, I have the demonstrated ability to learn quickly and adeptly leverage my nuanced background into any role. Dependable, excellent communication and organizational skills, highly adaptable, and incredibly effective at problem solving.

## Experience

## **Language and Culture Assistant Instructor**

Ministerio de Educación | Bailén, Spain

Oct 2019 - Oct 2020

- Adapt customized lesson plans for the classroom in coordination with lead instructor
- Effectively convey information both verbally and in writing;
- Monitor and assess students' progress and accordingly select suitable instructional methods;
- Coordinate and guide students to meet objectives and goals;
- Maintain a working knowledge of teaching standards and ensure these criteria are met

#### **Editorial Assistant**

Wolters Kluwer | Philadelphia, PA

Mar 2018 – Aug 2019

- Handled developmental editing tasks such as review analyses, permissions, and chapter mapping for online course modules;
- Created and maintained ISBNs/product records within proprietary title management software (Firebrand);
- Analyzed competitor products to aid in market development initiatives;
- Coordinated event planning tasks such as scheduling, catering, and reservations

#### **Human Resources Intern**

University Hospital | San Antonio, TX

*May 2014 – Mar 2017* 

- Responded to employee queries related to benefits and training;
- Maintained accurate employee, student, intern, and volunteer information in hospital database;
- Implemented new filing system to improve workspace organization

## Education

### Bachelor's in Social Thought and Political Economy

University of Massachusetts Amherst, Feb 2017

## Soft Skills

- Time management
- Task delegation
- Self-motivated
- Detail-oriented

## Hard Skills

- JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- Git and GitHub
- Database management
- Intermediate Spanish proficiency